In the distant past, there lived an era
of unrelenting violence and bloodshed.
It was a time before ninja had created any villages,
and shinobi lived in organized
clans where battle is all they knew.
Amongst the countless ninja clans,
the Uchiha stood out the most due to
their Sharingan and impressive chakra.
However, there was one clan that could stand up to them, and they were known as Senju.
The most famous member of the Senju
clan was their leader, Senju Hashirama.
Throughout their history, Uchiha and
Senju were constantly intertwined in battle.
However...
Both clans were exhausted, having to
endure endless battles, one after another.
They reached their limits.
The Senju approached the Uchiha in hopes for a truce, which the Uchiha agreed upon.
The two clans then built what is known today as the HIdden Leaf Village.
However, fearing that the Senju would oppress him and his clan,
Uchiha Madara attempted to rally support to overthrow Hashirama.
However, the Uchiha refused to help, so Madara abandoned the village.
In order to avenge what he felt was betrayal,
Madara eventually returned to battle against the HIdden Leaf Village.
The battle took place in an area that we know
today as the Valley of the End, and as for Madara...
It was Hashirama who emerged victorious.
Uchiha Madara lost the battle,
but the battle never truly ended.
However, the real battle has only just begun.